<project_specification>
  <project_name>SIMPLIFY — Marketing Landing Page</project_name>

  <overview>
    Build a high-converting marketing landing page for SIMPLIFY, an EdTech product by Simplify Inc.
    SIMPLIFY is a Canvas LTI plug-in that scans entire courses for accessibility and usability issues,
    maps findings to the rubrics faculty already use (CVC-OEI, Quality Matters, Peralta Equity), and
    offers one-click automated fixes. The landing page targets three audiences: faculty/instructors
    (primary buyers), instructional designers/accessibility coordinators (internal champions), and
    higher-ed administrators (budget holders). The page must communicate the product's value clearly,
    differentiate from competitors (UDOIT, Ally, Pope Tech), and drive demo requests and pilot signups.
    The design should feel modern, trustworthy, and education-forward — not corporate SaaS generic.
  </overview>

  <technology_stack>
    <frontend>
      <framework>Next.js 14+ (App Router, static export capable)</framework>
      <styling>Tailwind CSS 3.4+</styling>
      <animations>Framer Motion for scroll-triggered animations and micro-interactions</animations>
      <icons>Lucide React icon library</icons>
      <fonts>Google Fonts — Inter (body), Plus Jakarta Sans (headings)</fonts>
      <components>Radix UI primitives for accessible modals, tabs, accordions</components>
      <forms>React Hook Form + Zod validation for lead capture</forms>
      <analytics>Google Tag Manager container ready, conversion tracking pixels</analytics>
      <port>Launch on port 3000</port>
    </frontend>
    <backend>
      <form_handling>Next.js API routes or serverless function for form submissions</form_handling>
      <email>Resend or SendGrid integration for demo request notifications</email>
      <crm>Webhook to HubSpot/Salesforce for lead capture (configurable)</crm>
    </backend>
    <deployment>
      <platform>Vercel (primary) or Netlify</platform>
      <domain>simplifyedtech.com (placeholder)</domain>
      <ssl>Automatic via platform</ssl>
    </deployment>
  </technology_stack>

  <prerequisites>
    <environment_setup>
      - Node.js 18+ installed
      - pnpm or npm for package management
      - Environment variables: RESEND_API_KEY, CRM_WEBHOOK_URL, GTM_ID (all optional for dev)
      - All images use next/image with placeholder blur for performance
    </environment_setup>
  </prerequisites>

  <brand_identity>
    <company_name>Simplify</company_name>
    <product_name>SIMPLIFY</product_name>
    <tagline>One scan. Every rubric. Courses that work for everyone.</tagline>
    <sub_tagline>The Canvas plug-in that cleans up your courses — accessibility, usability, and equity in one place.</sub_tagline>

    <voice_and_tone>
      - Approachable and supportive, never punitive or compliance-heavy
      - Speaks to educators as peers, not as IT departments
      - Uses rubric language faculty already know (CVC-OEI, QM, POCR) — not raw WCAG jargon
      - Celebrates progress ("Your course improved 15 points") over shaming gaps
      - Confident but not arrogant — acknowledges the real challenges faculty face
    </voice_and_tone>

    <color_palette>
      <primary>
        <color name="simplify-blue" hex="#2563EB" usage="Primary CTAs, links, active states" />
        <color name="simplify-blue-dark" hex="#1E40AF" usage="Hover states, emphasis" />
        <color name="simplify-blue-light" hex="#DBEAFE" usage="Backgrounds, badges, highlights" />
      </primary>
      <secondary>
        <color name="simplify-green" hex="#059669" usage="Success states, score improvements, pass indicators" />
        <color name="simplify-green-light" hex="#D1FAE5" usage="Success backgrounds" />
        <color name="simplify-amber" hex="#D97706" usage="Warning states, partial-pass indicators" />
        <color name="simplify-amber-light" hex="#FEF3C7" usage="Warning backgrounds" />
        <color name="simplify-red" hex="#DC2626" usage="Critical issues, fail indicators" />
        <color name="simplify-red-light" hex="#FEE2E2" usage="Error backgrounds" />
      </secondary>
      <neutral>
        <color name="slate-900" hex="#0F172A" usage="Headings, primary text" />
        <color name="slate-700" hex="#334155" usage="Body text" />
        <color name="slate-500" hex="#64748B" usage="Secondary text, captions" />
        <color name="slate-200" hex="#E2E8F0" usage="Borders, dividers" />
        <color name="slate-50" hex="#F8FAFC" usage="Page background, alternating sections" />
        <color name="white" hex="#FFFFFF" usage="Card backgrounds, primary surfaces" />
      </neutral>
    </color_palette>

    <typography>
      <heading_font>Plus Jakarta Sans — weights 600 (semibold), 700 (bold), 800 (extrabold)</heading_font>
      <body_font>Inter — weights 400 (regular), 500 (medium), 600 (semibold)</body_font>
      <scale>
        - Hero H1: 4xl/5xl (36-48px), extrabold, tight tracking
        - Section H2: 3xl (30px), bold
        - Card H3: xl (20px), semibold
        - Body: base (16px), regular, relaxed leading (1.75)
        - Small: sm (14px), medium, for labels and captions
        - Code/technical: JetBrains Mono for any code snippets shown in product screenshots
      </scale>
    </typography>

    <imagery_style>
      - Product screenshots showing the SIMPLIFY dashboard UI (can be mockups/illustrations)
      - Diverse faculty and students in authentic higher-ed settings (not stock-photo corporate)
      - Abstract geometric patterns using the blue palette for section backgrounds
      - Iconography: line-style icons from Lucide, consistent 24px stroke
      - Illustrations: flat/semi-flat style with the blue/green/amber palette
      - NO generic stock photos of people staring at laptops
    </imagery_style>
  </brand_identity>

  <page_sections>
    <section id="nav" name="Navigation Bar">
      <description>
        Fixed top navigation bar with transparency that becomes solid on scroll.
      </description>
      <elements>
        - Simplify logo (left) — text wordmark "SIMPLIFY" in Plus Jakarta Sans extrabold
        - Nav links (center): Features, How It Works, Rubrics, Pricing, About
        - CTA buttons (right): "Watch Demo" (ghost/outline), "Request Pilot" (primary filled)
        - Mobile: hamburger menu with slide-out drawer
        - Scroll behavior: transparent bg at top, white bg with subtle shadow after 50px scroll
      </elements>
    </section>

    <section id="hero" name="Hero Section">
      <description>
        Full-viewport hero with the core value proposition. This is the most important section —
        it must immediately communicate WHAT SIMPLIFY does, WHO it's for, and WHY they should care.
      </description>
      <layout>Split layout — left text (60%), right product visual (40%)</layout>
      <content>
        <eyebrow>Canvas LTI Plug-in for Higher Education</eyebrow>
        <headline>Stop juggling accessibility tools. Start fixing your courses.</headline>
        <subheadline>
          SIMPLIFY scans your entire Canvas course against the rubrics you already use —
          CVC-OEI, Quality Matters, and Peralta Equity — then fixes issues with one click.
        </subheadline>
        <cta_primary>Request a Pilot → (leads to demo form)</cta_primary>
        <cta_secondary>See How It Works ↓ (smooth scroll to How It Works)</cta_secondary>
        <social_proof_bar>
          "Trusted by faculty at [X] California Community Colleges" with small institution logos
          (use placeholder logos for now — gray rounded rectangles)
        </social_proof_bar>
      </content>
      <visual>
        Animated product mockup showing the SIMPLIFY scan dashboard:
        - A browser frame containing the scan results UI
        - Animated score gauge going from 0 to 72/100
        - Severity badges popping in (3 Critical, 12 Serious, 24 Moderate, 8 Minor)
        - Rubric section bars filling in with progress
        - Subtle floating elements: checkmarks, accessibility icons
        Use CSS/SVG animation — not a video — for fast load and engagement.
      </visual>
      <background>
        Subtle gradient: white to slate-50. Optional: very faint grid/dot pattern.
      </background>
    </section>

    <section id="problem" name="Problem Statement / Pain Points">
      <description>
        Empathy-first section that names the exact frustrations faculty face. Uses the "problem →
        agitation → solution" framework. Three columns, each representing a pain point.
      </description>
      <layout>Section heading + 3-column card grid</layout>
      <content>
        <section_eyebrow>The Problem</section_eyebrow>
        <section_headline>Your courses deserve better than a patchwork of tools.</section_headline>
        <section_description>
          Faculty shouldn't need four different tools, three browser tabs, and a rubric
          spreadsheet just to make their courses accessible.
        </section_description>
        <pain_point id="1">
          <icon>Layers (overlapping tools)</icon>
          <title>Tool Overload</title>
          <description>
            UDOIT for HTML. Ally for documents. Pope Tech in the editor. The built-in checker
            for basics. You're running four tools that don't talk to each other.
          </description>
        </pain_point>
        <pain_point id="2">
          <icon>Languages (translation/disconnect)</icon>
          <title>Rubric Disconnect</title>
          <description>
            Your POCR reviewer says "Section D, Element 12." Your accessibility tool says
            "WCAG 2.1 SC 1.3.1." You're left playing translator between two worlds.
          </description>
        </pain_point>
        <pain_point id="3">
          <icon>MousePointerClick (manual work)</icon>
          <title>Flag Without Fix</title>
          <description>
            Most tools tell you what's wrong — then leave you to fix it manually, page by page,
            image by image, table by table. Who has time for that?
          </description>
        </pain_point>
      </content>
    </section>

    <section id="solution" name="Solution Overview / Product Introduction">
      <description>
        Transition section that introduces SIMPLIFY as the answer to the problems above.
        Big visual impact — full-width product screenshot with overlaid feature callouts.
      </description>
      <layout>Centered text block above a large product screenshot/mockup</layout>
      <content>
        <section_eyebrow>The Solution</section_eyebrow>
        <section_headline>One scan. Every rubric. One-click fixes.</section_headline>
        <section_description>
          SIMPLIFY replaces your patchwork of tools with a single Canvas plug-in that scans your
          entire course, reports issues in the rubric language you already use, and fixes the most
          common problems automatically.
        </section_description>
        <product_screenshot>
          Large, detailed mockup of the SIMPLIFY dashboard showing:
          - Overall score (72/100) with progress ring
          - Severity breakdown cards (Critical: 3, Serious: 12, Moderate: 24, Minor: 8)
          - Rubric section breakdown (A: Content 80%, B: Interaction 60%, C: Assessment 75%, D: Accessibility 65%)
          - "Fix All Auto-Fixable (18)" button highlighted
          - "Export Report" and "Schedule Rescan" secondary buttons
          Annotated with callout labels pointing to key features.
        </product_screenshot>
      </content>
      <background>slate-50 background with subtle gradient</background>
    </section>

    <section id="features" name="Core Features Deep Dive">
      <description>
        Detailed feature showcase. Uses alternating left-right layout (feature text + visual) for
        each of the four core capabilities. Each feature gets its own visual treatment.
      </description>
      <layout>Alternating rows — odd rows: text left / visual right; even rows: visual left / text right</layout>
      <content>
        <feature id="1">
          <icon>ScanSearch</icon>
          <eyebrow>Course Scanner</eyebrow>
          <title>Full-course scan in seconds</title>
          <description>
            SIMPLIFY scans every page, assignment, discussion, quiz, syllabus, and uploaded
            document in your course. Not just the page you're editing — everything, all at once.
          </description>
          <bullets>
            - WCAG 2.1 AA compliance checks on all HTML content
            - PDF, DOCX, and PPTX document accessibility analysis
            - Broken link detection across your entire course
            - Course structure validation (modules, navigation, welcome page)
          </bullets>
          <visual>
            Mockup showing a scan in progress — progress bar with content type icons
            (pages, assignments, files) being checked off as the scan proceeds.
          </visual>
        </feature>

        <feature id="2">
          <icon>BookOpen</icon>
          <eyebrow>Rubric-Aligned Reports</eyebrow>
          <title>Reports that speak your rubric's language</title>
          <description>
            Stop translating WCAG codes into rubric elements. SIMPLIFY maps every issue directly
            to the CVC-OEI, Quality Matters, or Peralta rubric standards your institution uses.
          </description>
          <bullets>
            - Choose your rubric: CVC-OEI, QM, Peralta, or all three
            - Issues grouped by rubric section (not WCAG success criteria)
            - Element-level scoring: Aligned / Partially Aligned / Not Aligned
            - Export PDF reports ready for POCR or QM submission
          </bullets>
          <visual>
            Mockup of the rubric-aligned report view showing CVC-OEI sections A-D with
            element-level pass/fail indicators and a "Download PDF" button.
          </visual>
        </feature>

        <feature id="3">
          <icon>Wand2</icon>
          <eyebrow>One-Click Fixes</eyebrow>
          <title>Don't just find problems — fix them</title>
          <description>
            For the most common accessibility issues, SIMPLIFY offers automated fixes you can
            preview, edit, and apply without ever leaving the tool. Bulk operations let you
            fix entire categories at once.
          </description>
          <bullets>
            - AI-generated alt text suggestions (editable before applying)
            - Heading hierarchy repair with live preview
            - Color contrast fixes with compliant alternatives
            - Table header insertion and link text improvements
            - "Fix All" for batch operations — with full undo/rollback
          </bullets>
          <visual>
            Mockup of the fix interface: image with missing alt text, AI-suggested description,
            Edit/Apply/Skip buttons, and a before/after preview toggle.
          </visual>
        </feature>

        <feature id="4">
          <icon>BarChart3</icon>
          <eyebrow>Institutional Dashboard</eyebrow>
          <title>See the big picture across your institution</title>
          <description>
            Administrators and instructional designers get aggregate views across departments,
            divisions, and the entire institution. Track compliance trends across terms and
            prioritize support where it's needed most.
          </description>
          <bullets>
            - Department and division-level compliance aggregation
            - Term-over-term trend reporting (Fall → Spring → Summer)
            - Faculty support queue for instructional designers
            - Benchmark targets with progress tracking
            - Role-based access — aggregate data for admins, course details for instructors
          </bullets>
          <visual>
            Mockup of the admin dashboard: bar chart showing department compliance percentages,
            trend line across terms, and a top-10 "needs attention" course list.
          </visual>
        </feature>
      </content>
    </section>

    <section id="how-it-works" name="How It Works (3-Step Process)">
      <description>
        Simple 3-step process strip that shows how quick and easy it is to use SIMPLIFY.
        Reduces cognitive load and demonstrates low friction.
      </description>
      <layout>Horizontal 3-column with numbered steps, connected by arrows/lines</layout>
      <content>
        <section_eyebrow>How It Works</section_eyebrow>
        <section_headline>Three steps to a better course.</section_headline>
        <step number="1">
          <icon>MousePointerClick</icon>
          <title>Scan</title>
          <description>
            Launch SIMPLIFY from your Canvas course navigation. Select your rubric(s) and
            click "Scan Course." We'll check everything in seconds.
          </description>
        </step>
        <step number="2">
          <icon>FileSearch</icon>
          <title>Review</title>
          <description>
            See results organized by rubric section — not WCAG codes. Drill into any issue
            to see exactly what's wrong and where, with plain-language explanations.
          </description>
        </step>
        <step number="3">
          <icon>Sparkles</icon>
          <title>Fix</title>
          <description>
            Apply one-click fixes for common issues, or follow guided instructions for
            everything else. Watch your score climb in real time.
          </description>
        </step>
      </content>
      <background>White with subtle connecting line/arrow graphic between steps</background>
    </section>

    <section id="rubrics" name="Framework / Rubric Alignment">
      <description>
        Credibility section showing alignment with the three major rubrics. Uses a tabbed
        interface to let visitors explore each rubric's coverage. This is critical for
        decision-makers who need to know the tool maps to their specific rubric.
      </description>
      <layout>Section heading + tabbed content area (3 tabs)</layout>
      <content>
        <section_eyebrow>Framework Alignment</section_eyebrow>
        <section_headline>Built on the rubrics you already trust.</section_headline>
        <section_description>
          Every scan rule in SIMPLIFY maps directly to one or more elements from these
          evidence-based course quality and equity frameworks.
        </section_description>
        <tab id="cvc-oei">
          <tab_title>CVC-OEI</tab_title>
          <tab_subtitle>California Virtual Campus — Online Education Initiative</tab_subtitle>
          <content>
            - 44 elements across 4 sections (A: Content, B: Interaction, C: Assessment, D: Accessibility)
            - High automation coverage for Section A (navigation, structure) and Section D (WCAG compliance)
            - Medium coverage for Sections B and C with guided checklists
            - PDF reports formatted for POCR submission
          </content>
          <coverage_visual>
            4 horizontal bars showing coverage percentage per section:
            A: Content Presentation — 85% automated
            B: Interaction — 50% automated + checklist
            C: Assessment — 40% automated + checklist
            D: Accessibility — 95% automated
          </coverage_visual>
        </tab>
        <tab id="quality-matters">
          <tab_title>Quality Matters</tab_title>
          <tab_subtitle>QM Higher Education Rubric, 7th Edition</tab_subtitle>
          <content>
            - 8 General Standards with 44 Specific Review Standards
            - Strong automation for Standard 8 (Accessibility and Usability)
            - Automatable indicators for Standards 1-7 (welcome page, objectives, broken links, support links)
            - PDF reports formatted for QM review submission
          </content>
          <coverage_visual>
            8 horizontal bars showing coverage per standard:
            1: Course Overview — 60%
            2: Learning Objectives — 45%
            3: Assessment — 40%
            4: Instructional Materials — 55%
            5: Learning Activities — 35%
            6: Course Technology — 50%
            7: Learner Support — 60%
            8: Accessibility — 95%
          </coverage_visual>
        </tab>
        <tab id="peralta">
          <tab_title>Peralta Equity</tab_title>
          <tab_subtitle>Peralta Online Equity Rubric 3.0</tab_subtitle>
          <content>
            - 8 equity elements (E1-E8) designed to complement the CVC-OEI rubric
            - Automated checks for E1 (Technology), E2 (Resources), E3 (UDL), and E8 (Belonging)
            - Guided self-assessment checklists for E4-E7 (Diversity, Representation, Bias, Meaning)
            - The only Canvas tool that addresses equity rubric elements
          </content>
          <coverage_visual>
            8 elements with icons showing automated vs. checklist:
            E1: Technology — Automated
            E2: Resources — Automated
            E3: UDL — Automated
            E4: Diversity — Guided Checklist
            E5: Images — Guided Checklist
            E6: Bias — Guided Checklist
            E7: Meaning — Guided Checklist
            E8: Belonging — Automated + Checklist
          </coverage_visual>
        </tab>
      </content>
    </section>

    <section id="comparison" name="Competitive Comparison">
      <description>
        Feature comparison table showing SIMPLIFY vs. the existing tools (UDOIT, Ally, Pope Tech,
        Canvas built-in). This section directly addresses the "why switch?" question for
        institutions already using other tools.
      </description>
      <layout>Section heading + responsive comparison table</layout>
      <content>
        <section_eyebrow>Why SIMPLIFY?</section_eyebrow>
        <section_headline>Everything you need. Nothing you don't.</section_headline>
        <comparison_table>
          <columns>Feature, SIMPLIFY, UDOIT, Ally, Pope Tech, Canvas Built-in</columns>
          <rows>
            <row feature="Full-course HTML scan" simplify="yes" udoit="yes" ally="no" pope_tech="no" canvas="no" />
            <row feature="Document scanning (PDF, DOCX)" simplify="yes" udoit="partial" ally="yes" pope_tech="no" canvas="no" />
            <row feature="Course structure analysis" simplify="yes" udoit="no" ally="no" pope_tech="no" canvas="no" />
            <row feature="CVC-OEI rubric alignment" simplify="yes" udoit="no" ally="no" pope_tech="no" canvas="no" />
            <row feature="Quality Matters alignment" simplify="yes" udoit="no" ally="no" pope_tech="no" canvas="no" />
            <row feature="Peralta Equity rubric" simplify="yes" udoit="no" ally="no" pope_tech="no" canvas="no" />
            <row feature="One-click auto-fixes" simplify="yes" udoit="partial" ally="no" pope_tech="no" canvas="no" />
            <row feature="AI-generated alt text" simplify="yes" udoit="no" ally="no" pope_tech="no" canvas="no" />
            <row feature="Bulk fix operations" simplify="yes" udoit="no" ally="no" pope_tech="no" canvas="no" />
            <row feature="Institutional dashboard" simplify="yes" udoit="no" ally="partial" pope_tech="yes" canvas="no" />
            <row feature="PDF report export (POCR/QM)" simplify="yes" udoit="no" ally="no" pope_tech="no" canvas="no" />
            <row feature="UDL content variety check" simplify="yes" udoit="no" ally="no" pope_tech="no" canvas="no" />
            <row feature="Equity self-assessment" simplify="yes" udoit="no" ally="no" pope_tech="no" canvas="no" />
            <row feature="Progress tracking over time" simplify="yes" udoit="no" ally="partial" pope_tech="partial" canvas="no" />
          </rows>
        </comparison_table>
      </content>
      <design_notes>
        - SIMPLIFY column highlighted with blue background
        - Yes = green checkmark, No = gray dash, Partial = amber half-circle
        - On mobile: convert to stacked cards comparing SIMPLIFY vs. one competitor at a time
      </design_notes>
    </section>

    <section id="testimonials" name="Social Proof / Testimonials">
      <description>
        Testimonial carousel featuring quotes from faculty, instructional designers, and
        administrators. Uses placeholder quotes for now that reflect real personas.
      </description>
      <layout>Carousel with 3 visible cards at desktop, 1 at mobile, auto-advance</layout>
      <content>
        <section_eyebrow>What Educators Say</section_eyebrow>
        <section_headline>Faculty love it. Admins trust it.</section_headline>
        <testimonial id="1">
          <quote>
            I used to spend an entire prep week running UDOIT and fixing things page by page.
            SIMPLIFY did my whole course in 30 seconds and fixed half the issues automatically.
            I got my weekend back.
          </quote>
          <author>Dr. Maria Santos</author>
          <role>Biology Faculty</role>
          <institution>Bay Area Community College (placeholder)</institution>
        </testimonial>
        <testimonial id="2">
          <quote>
            The rubric-aligned reports are a game-changer for POCR. I can hand faculty a report
            that maps directly to the CVC-OEI elements instead of making them decode WCAG codes.
          </quote>
          <author>James Chen</author>
          <role>Instructional Designer</role>
          <institution>Central Valley College District (placeholder)</institution>
        </testimonial>
        <testimonial id="3">
          <quote>
            For the first time, I can tell our accreditor exactly what percentage of our courses
            meet accessibility standards — and show them the improvement trend. That used to be
            a manual audit that took weeks.
          </quote>
          <author>Dr. Aisha Thompson</author>
          <role>VP of Instruction</role>
          <institution>Southern California CC District (placeholder)</institution>
        </testimonial>
        <testimonial id="4">
          <quote>
            The Peralta equity checklists opened my eyes to things I wasn't even thinking about.
            It's not just about compliance — it's about whether my course actually works for
            all of my students.
          </quote>
          <author>Prof. David Reyes</author>
          <role>English Faculty</role>
          <institution>Northern California College (placeholder)</institution>
        </testimonial>
      </content>
    </section>

    <section id="stats" name="Impact Statistics / By the Numbers">
      <description>
        Bold statistics strip with animated counters that convey product impact.
        Numbers should trigger count-up animation when scrolled into view.
      </description>
      <layout>4-column horizontal strip on colored background</layout>
      <content>
        <stat id="1">
          <number>50%</number>
          <label>Less time on accessibility remediation</label>
        </stat>
        <stat id="2">
          <number>40%+</number>
          <label>Of issues auto-fixed with one click</label>
        </stat>
        <stat id="3">
          <number>35+</number>
          <label>Scan rules mapped across 3 rubrics</label>
        </stat>
        <stat id="4">
          <number>30 sec</number>
          <label>Average full-course scan time</label>
        </stat>
      </content>
      <background>simplify-blue gradient (left to right, blue-dark to blue)</background>
      <text_color>white</text_color>
    </section>

    <section id="pricing" name="Pricing">
      <description>
        Simple, transparent pricing section. EdTech buyers need to see pricing early —
        hiding it behind "contact sales" loses trust. Offer a free pilot and two tiers.
      </description>
      <layout>3-column pricing cards</layout>
      <content>
        <section_eyebrow>Pricing</section_eyebrow>
        <section_headline>Start with a free pilot. Scale when you're ready.</section_headline>
        <plan id="pilot">
          <name>Pilot</name>
          <price>Free</price>
          <period>60 days, up to 10 courses</period>
          <description>Try SIMPLIFY risk-free with your real courses.</description>
          <features>
            - Full-course scanning (HTML content)
            - CVC-OEI + QM rubric reporting
            - One-click fixes (alt text, headings, contrast, tables)
            - PDF report export
            - Email support
          </features>
          <cta>Start Free Pilot</cta>
          <cta_style>outline / secondary</cta_style>
        </plan>
        <plan id="institution" featured="true">
          <name>Institution</name>
          <price>Custom</price>
          <period>per institution / per year</period>
          <description>Full SIMPLIFY for your entire institution.</description>
          <features>
            - Everything in Pilot, plus:
            - Document scanning (PDF, DOCX, PPTX)
            - Peralta Equity rubric + UDL checks
            - Institutional admin dashboard
            - Scheduled scans + email summaries
            - Dedicated onboarding + training
            - Priority support + SLA
          </features>
          <cta>Request a Quote</cta>
          <cta_style>primary / filled</cta_style>
          <badge>Most Popular</badge>
        </plan>
        <plan id="enterprise">
          <name>Enterprise</name>
          <price>Custom</price>
          <period>multi-campus / district</period>
          <description>For districts and multi-college systems.</description>
          <features>
            - Everything in Institution, plus:
            - Multi-campus aggregate dashboards
            - Custom rubric configurations
            - API access + webhooks
            - SSO integration (SAML/CAS)
            - Dedicated success manager
            - SOC 2 compliance documentation
          </features>
          <cta>Contact Sales</cta>
          <cta_style>outline / secondary</cta_style>
        </plan>
      </content>
    </section>

    <section id="faq" name="Frequently Asked Questions">
      <description>
        Accordion-style FAQ addressing the most common objections and questions from
        faculty, instructional designers, and administrators.
      </description>
      <layout>Section heading + accordion (expandable items)</layout>
      <content>
        <section_eyebrow>FAQ</section_eyebrow>
        <section_headline>Questions? We've got answers.</section_headline>
        <faq id="1">
          <question>How is SIMPLIFY different from UDOIT?</question>
          <answer>
            UDOIT scans native HTML content in Canvas, which is great — but it doesn't scan
            uploaded documents (PDFs, Word files), doesn't map findings to CVC-OEI or QM rubric
            elements, and offers limited auto-fix capabilities. SIMPLIFY does all of that in a
            single tool, plus adds equity rubric alignment and institutional dashboards.
          </answer>
        </faq>
        <faq id="2">
          <question>Does SIMPLIFY replace Ally?</question>
          <answer>
            Ally is strong at scanning uploaded documents and providing alternative formats to
            students. SIMPLIFY complements or replaces Ally by adding course-wide HTML scanning,
            rubric-aligned reporting, one-click fixes, and course structure analysis. If you need
            student-facing alternative formats (e.g., audio versions of PDFs), Ally still provides
            that. For everything else, SIMPLIFY covers it.
          </answer>
        </faq>
        <faq id="3">
          <question>What rubrics does SIMPLIFY support?</question>
          <answer>
            At launch, SIMPLIFY supports three frameworks: the CVC-OEI Course Design Rubric
            (Sections A-D), the Quality Matters Higher Education Rubric (8 Standards), and the
            Peralta Online Equity Rubric 3.0 (Elements E1-E8). You can run reports against any
            one rubric or all three simultaneously.
          </answer>
        </faq>
        <faq id="4">
          <question>Will SIMPLIFY change my course content without my approval?</question>
          <answer>
            Never. Every auto-fix is previewed before you apply it. You can edit suggestions,
            skip issues, or dismiss them entirely. Bulk "Fix All" operations show you exactly
            what will change before you confirm. And every fix is fully reversible — we maintain
            a complete change log with one-click rollback.
          </answer>
        </faq>
        <faq id="5">
          <question>How long does a scan take?</question>
          <answer>
            A typical 16-week course with 50-100 content items scans in about 30 seconds.
            Larger courses with many uploaded documents may take 1-2 minutes. You can
            also schedule automatic weekly scans that run in the background and email you
            a summary report.
          </answer>
        </faq>
        <faq id="6">
          <question>Is student data accessed or stored?</question>
          <answer>
            No. SIMPLIFY only accesses course content — pages, assignments, files, and structure.
            It never accesses student submissions, grades, or personal information. We are fully
            FERPA compliant and pursuing SOC 2 Type II certification.
          </answer>
        </faq>
        <faq id="7">
          <question>How does the pilot work?</question>
          <answer>
            The free pilot gives you 60 days with up to 10 courses. Your institution's Canvas
            admin installs SIMPLIFY as an LTI tool (takes about 5 minutes). Faculty can then
            launch it from any course's navigation menu. No credit card required. At the end
            of the pilot, you can continue with an institutional license or simply uninstall.
          </answer>
        </faq>
        <faq id="8">
          <question>Does it work with other LMS platforms?</question>
          <answer>
            SIMPLIFY launches with Canvas LMS support. Support for Moodle, Blackboard Ultra,
            and Brightspace is on our roadmap for 2027. If you're interested in a non-Canvas
            LMS, let us know — it helps us prioritize.
          </answer>
        </faq>
      </content>
    </section>

    <section id="cta" name="Final Call-to-Action">
      <description>
        Strong closing CTA section with a demo request form. This is where the conversion happens.
        The form should be simple — name, email, institution, role, and an optional message.
      </description>
      <layout>Split — left: compelling copy; right: form</layout>
      <content>
        <headline>Ready to simplify accessibility?</headline>
        <subheadline>
          Join the pilot program and see how SIMPLIFY transforms your course cleanup workflow.
          Free for 60 days. No credit card required. Setup takes 5 minutes.
        </subheadline>
        <form_fields>
          <field name="name" type="text" label="Full Name" required="true" placeholder="Dr. Jane Smith" />
          <field name="email" type="email" label="Work Email" required="true" placeholder="jsmith@college.edu" />
          <field name="institution" type="text" label="Institution" required="true" placeholder="Bay Area Community College" />
          <field name="role" type="select" label="Your Role" required="true">
            <option>Faculty / Instructor</option>
            <option>Instructional Designer</option>
            <option>Accessibility Coordinator</option>
            <option>Department Chair</option>
            <option>Dean / VP of Instruction</option>
            <option>IT / Canvas Admin</option>
            <option>Other</option>
          </field>
          <field name="courses" type="select" label="How many courses?" required="false">
            <option>1-5</option>
            <option>6-20</option>
            <option>21-100</option>
            <option>100+</option>
          </field>
          <field name="message" type="textarea" label="Anything else we should know?" required="false"
                 placeholder="E.g., we're preparing for POCR review, we currently use UDOIT..." />
        </form_fields>
        <submit_button>Request Free Pilot →</submit_button>
        <privacy_note>
          We respect your privacy. Your information is used only to set up your pilot
          and will never be shared with third parties.
        </privacy_note>
      </content>
      <background>slate-50 with subtle blue accent border or gradient</background>
    </section>

    <section id="footer" name="Footer">
      <description>Standard marketing footer with navigation, legal links, and social proof.</description>
      <layout>4-column footer grid</layout>
      <content>
        <column id="brand">
          - SIMPLIFY logo wordmark
          - One-line description: "Accessible, usable, equitable courses — simplified."
          - Social media icons (LinkedIn, Twitter/X) — placeholder links
        </column>
        <column id="product">
          <title>Product</title>
          - Features
          - How It Works
          - Pricing
          - Rubric Alignment
          - Roadmap (placeholder)
        </column>
        <column id="resources">
          <title>Resources</title>
          - Documentation (placeholder)
          - Blog (placeholder)
          - CVC-OEI Rubric (external link)
          - Quality Matters (external link)
          - Peralta Equity Rubric (external link)
        </column>
        <column id="company">
          <title>Company</title>
          - About (placeholder)
          - Contact
          - Privacy Policy (placeholder)
          - Terms of Service (placeholder)
          - Accessibility Statement (placeholder)
        </column>
        <bottom_bar>
          - © 2026 Simplify Inc. All rights reserved.
          - "Built with accessibility in mind" badge
        </bottom_bar>
      </content>
    </section>
  </page_sections>

  <design_system>
    <layout_principles>
      - Max content width: 1280px, centered with auto margins
      - Section padding: py-20 (80px) on desktop, py-12 (48px) on mobile
      - Card grid gaps: gap-8 (32px)
      - Consistent section rhythm: eyebrow → headline → description → content
      - Alternating section backgrounds: white → slate-50 → white → slate-50
    </layout_principles>

    <component_specs>
      <buttons>
        <primary>
          bg-simplify-blue text-white font-semibold px-8 py-3 rounded-lg
          hover:bg-simplify-blue-dark transition-colors duration-200
          shadow-sm hover:shadow-md
        </primary>
        <secondary>
          border-2 border-simplify-blue text-simplify-blue font-semibold px-8 py-3 rounded-lg
          hover:bg-simplify-blue hover:text-white transition-all duration-200
        </secondary>
        <ghost>
          text-simplify-blue font-medium hover:underline
        </ghost>
      </buttons>

      <cards>
        bg-white rounded-2xl border border-slate-200 p-8
        shadow-sm hover:shadow-md transition-shadow duration-200
      </cards>

      <badges>
        inline-flex items-center px-3 py-1 rounded-full text-sm font-medium
        Variants: blue (info), green (success), amber (warning), red (critical)
      </badges>

      <section_eyebrow>
        text-simplify-blue font-semibold text-sm uppercase tracking-widest mb-3
      </section_eyebrow>

      <section_headline>
        text-slate-900 font-bold text-3xl md:text-4xl leading-tight mb-4
        font-family: Plus Jakarta Sans
      </section_headline>

      <section_description>
        text-slate-600 text-lg md:text-xl leading-relaxed max-w-3xl mx-auto mb-12
      </section_description>
    </component_specs>

    <animations>
      <scroll_reveal>
        Framer Motion: elements fade up (y: 20 → 0, opacity: 0 → 1) as they enter viewport.
        Stagger children by 100ms within card grids.
        Duration: 500ms. Easing: easeOut.
        Trigger: when element is 20% visible (whileInView with viewport once: true).
      </scroll_reveal>
      <counter>
        Stats section: numbers count up from 0 to target value over 2 seconds.
        Trigger on scroll into view. Use requestAnimationFrame or framer-motion useMotionValue.
      </counter>
      <hero_product>
        Score gauge: animate from 0 to 72 over 1.5 seconds with easeOut.
        Severity badges: stagger in with scale(0.8 → 1) + fade, 200ms delay between each.
        Section bars: width grows from 0% to target over 1 second, staggered.
      </hero_product>
      <hover>
        Cards: translateY(-2px) + shadow increase on hover, 200ms transition.
        Buttons: background-color transition, 150ms.
        Links: underline slide-in from left, 200ms.
      </hover>
      <tab_switch>
        Rubric tabs: content cross-fades with 200ms transition. Active tab gets blue underline
        that slides to follow selection.
      </tab_switch>
    </animations>

    <responsive_breakpoints>
      - Mobile: 0-639px (single column, stacked layout, hamburger nav)
      - Tablet: 640-1023px (2 columns where applicable, condensed spacing)
      - Desktop: 1024px+ (full layout as designed, max-w-7xl container)
      - Large: 1280px+ (additional breathing room, larger hero text)
    </responsive_breakpoints>

    <accessibility_requirements>
      - WCAG 2.1 AA compliant (the landing page itself must be accessible — it's an accessibility product!)
      - All images have descriptive alt text
      - Color contrast minimum 4.5:1 for body text, 3:1 for large text
      - Keyboard navigable: all interactive elements reachable via Tab, activated via Enter/Space
      - Focus indicators visible on all interactive elements (2px blue outline)
      - Skip navigation link at page top
      - Reduced motion: respect prefers-reduced-motion by disabling scroll animations
      - Semantic HTML: proper heading hierarchy (single H1 in hero, H2 for sections, H3 for cards)
      - Form fields: visible labels, error messages associated with fields, aria-describedby for hints
      - Testimonial carousel: pause-on-hover, prev/next buttons, aria-live region
    </accessibility_requirements>
  </design_system>

  <seo_and_metadata>
    <title>SIMPLIFY — Canvas Course Accessibility &amp; Usability Plug-in | Simplify EdTech</title>
    <meta_description>
      SIMPLIFY is a Canvas LTI plug-in that scans your courses for accessibility and usability issues,
      reports against CVC-OEI, Quality Matters, and Peralta rubrics, and offers one-click fixes.
      Free pilot available.
    </meta_description>
    <og_title>SIMPLIFY — Stop juggling accessibility tools. Start fixing your courses.</og_title>
    <og_description>
      One Canvas plug-in that scans, reports, and fixes accessibility issues — aligned to the
      rubrics you already use. Free 60-day pilot.
    </og_description>
    <og_image>Social share card with SIMPLIFY logo, tagline, and dashboard screenshot mockup</og_image>
    <keywords>
      Canvas LMS accessibility, course accessibility checker, CVC-OEI rubric tool, Quality Matters
      accessibility, Peralta equity rubric, Canvas LTI plugin, WCAG course compliance, online course
      accessibility, POCR accessibility, higher education accessibility tool, course design rubric,
      accessible course design, Canvas accessibility plugin, UDOIT alternative, Ally alternative
    </keywords>
    <structured_data>
      - Organization schema for Simplify Inc.
      - SoftwareApplication schema for SIMPLIFY product
      - FAQPage schema for the FAQ section
    </structured_data>
  </seo_and_metadata>

  <key_interactions>
    <navigation_flow>
      1. User arrives on page (likely from search, conference link, or referral)
      2. Hero communicates value prop in &lt; 5 seconds
      3. Social proof bar builds immediate credibility
      4. Scroll reveals problem framing (user sees their own pain reflected)
      5. Solution section + features build desire
      6. Rubric tabs let them verify their specific rubric is supported
      7. Comparison table removes "why not stick with UDOIT/Ally" objection
      8. Testimonials from peers build trust
      9. Stats strip reinforces impact
      10. Pricing removes cost anxiety (free pilot!)
      11. FAQ handles remaining objections
      12. Final CTA captures the lead
    </navigation_flow>

    <form_submission_flow>
      1. User fills out form fields (client-side validation via Zod)
      2. Clicks "Request Free Pilot"
      3. Button shows loading spinner
      4. POST to /api/pilot-request with form data
      5. Server validates, stores in database, sends webhook to CRM, sends confirmation email
      6. Form replaced with success message: "You're in! Check your email for next steps."
      7. Success state includes: confirmation checkmark animation, what to expect next, link to documentation
      8. GTM conversion event fires for ad tracking
    </form_submission_flow>

    <nav_scroll_behavior>
      1. Nav links use smooth scroll to section anchors
      2. Active section highlighted in nav based on scroll position (Intersection Observer)
      3. "Watch Demo" opens a modal with embedded video (or placeholder)
      4. "Request Pilot" smooth scrolls to final CTA form
      5. Mobile nav: hamburger opens slide-out drawer, links close drawer after click
    </nav_scroll_behavior>
  </key_interactions>

  <implementation_steps>
    <step number="1">
      <title>Project Setup and Foundation</title>
      <tasks>
        - Initialize Next.js 14+ project with App Router
        - Configure Tailwind CSS with custom theme (colors, fonts, spacing from brand identity)
        - Install dependencies: framer-motion, lucide-react, @radix-ui/react-accordion, @radix-ui/react-tabs, react-hook-form, zod
        - Set up Google Fonts (Inter, Plus Jakarta Sans)
        - Create layout.tsx with metadata, font loading, and global styles
        - Create reusable component structure: /components/ui/, /components/sections/
        - Set up tailwind.config.ts with custom colors (simplify-blue, etc.) and font families
      </tasks>
    </step>

    <step number="2">
      <title>Navigation and Hero Section</title>
      <tasks>
        - Build responsive Navbar component with scroll-triggered bg transition
        - Implement mobile hamburger menu with slide-out drawer
        - Build Hero section with split layout (text left, product visual right)
        - Create animated product mockup SVG/CSS (score gauge, severity badges, section bars)
        - Add social proof bar with placeholder institution logos
        - Implement smooth-scroll navigation for all anchor links
        - Add skip-navigation link for accessibility
      </tasks>
    </step>

    <step number="3">
      <title>Problem and Solution Sections</title>
      <tasks>
        - Build Problem section with 3-column pain point cards
        - Add Lucide icons for each pain point
        - Build Solution section with centered text + large product screenshot mockup
        - Create product screenshot as a styled HTML/CSS component (not an image) for flexibility
        - Add scroll-reveal animations (Framer Motion) for cards and sections
      </tasks>
    </step>

    <step number="4">
      <title>Features Deep Dive</title>
      <tasks>
        - Build alternating feature rows component (text + visual, flipping sides)
        - Create 4 feature sections with icons, bullets, and mockup visuals
        - Build feature visual mockups as styled components:
          1. Scan progress indicator mockup
          2. Rubric-aligned report mockup
          3. Fix interface mockup (image + AI suggestion + buttons)
          4. Admin dashboard chart mockup
        - Add scroll-triggered stagger animations for bullet points
      </tasks>
    </step>

    <step number="5">
      <title>How It Works and Rubric Alignment</title>
      <tasks>
        - Build 3-step process section with numbered steps and connecting line graphic
        - Build rubric alignment section with Radix UI Tabs
        - Create 3 tab panels (CVC-OEI, Quality Matters, Peralta) with coverage visualizations
        - Build animated coverage bar components (fills to percentage on scroll into view)
        - Style active tab indicator with sliding underline animation
      </tasks>
    </step>

    <step number="6">
      <title>Comparison Table and Testimonials</title>
      <tasks>
        - Build responsive comparison table (table on desktop, stacked cards on mobile)
        - Style checkmark/dash/partial icons for feature rows
        - Highlight SIMPLIFY column with blue background
        - Build testimonial carousel with auto-advance, pause on hover
        - Add previous/next navigation buttons and dot indicators
        - Ensure carousel is accessible (aria-live, keyboard controls)
      </tasks>
    </step>

    <step number="7">
      <title>Stats, Pricing, and FAQ</title>
      <tasks>
        - Build stats strip with animated count-up numbers (trigger on scroll)
        - Build 3-column pricing cards with "Most Popular" badge on Institution plan
        - Style pricing features with checkmark lists
        - Build FAQ section with Radix UI Accordion (animated expand/collapse)
        - Ensure accordion is keyboard accessible and uses proper ARIA attributes
      </tasks>
    </step>

    <step number="8">
      <title>CTA Form and Footer</title>
      <tasks>
        - Build final CTA section with split layout (copy left, form right)
        - Implement form with React Hook Form + Zod validation
        - Add client-side validation with inline error messages
        - Create API route (/api/pilot-request) for form submission
        - Add success state with confirmation animation
        - Build 4-column footer with navigation links
        - Add copyright bar with accessibility statement badge
      </tasks>
    </step>

    <step number="9">
      <title>Polish, Performance, and SEO</title>
      <tasks>
        - Audit all animations for prefers-reduced-motion support
        - Run Lighthouse audit — target 95+ on all categories
        - Verify WCAG 2.1 AA compliance with axe-core
        - Test full keyboard navigation flow
        - Test on mobile devices (iOS Safari, Android Chrome)
        - Add structured data (Organization, SoftwareApplication, FAQPage)
        - Add Open Graph and Twitter Card meta tags
        - Optimize images with next/image and WebP format
        - Minify and tree-shake CSS/JS
        - Test form submission end-to-end
        - Cross-browser testing (Chrome, Firefox, Safari, Edge)
      </tasks>
    </step>
  </implementation_steps>

  <success_criteria>
    <design_quality>
      - Visually distinctive — does NOT look like a generic SaaS template
      - Consistent with brand identity (blue palette, Plus Jakarta Sans headings, Inter body)
      - Product mockups feel authentic and detailed (not placeholder boxes)
      - Animations enhance understanding without being distracting
      - Whitespace and rhythm create comfortable reading experience
    </design_quality>

    <conversion_optimization>
      - Primary CTA ("Request a Pilot") visible above the fold and in nav
      - Clear value prop communicated within 5 seconds of landing
      - Problem section creates recognition ("that's me!")
      - Comparison table handles the "why switch?" objection
      - FAQ handles remaining objections before they reach the form
      - Form is short enough (6 fields, 2 optional) to not deter submissions
      - Social proof (testimonials, stats, institution logos) builds trust throughout
    </conversion_optimization>

    <technical_quality>
      - Lighthouse scores: Performance 95+, Accessibility 100, Best Practices 95+, SEO 100
      - Core Web Vitals: LCP &lt; 2.5s, FID &lt; 100ms, CLS &lt; 0.1
      - Fully responsive from 320px to 2560px
      - WCAG 2.1 AA compliant (0 axe-core violations)
      - Forms work with JavaScript disabled (progressive enhancement)
      - Page loads in under 3 seconds on 3G connection
    </technical_quality>

    <accessibility>
      - The landing page for an accessibility product MUST itself be fully accessible
      - Single H1, proper heading hierarchy throughout
      - All interactive elements keyboard accessible
      - Focus visible on all focusable elements
      - Color contrast meets AA minimums everywhere
      - Screen reader tested (VoiceOver on macOS at minimum)
      - Reduced motion mode functional
      - Form errors announced to screen readers
    </accessibility>

    <content_quality>
      - Copy speaks to educators, not IT departments
      - Rubric terminology used correctly (CVC-OEI sections, QM standards, Peralta elements)
      - Pain points resonate with actual faculty experience
      - No jargon without context (WCAG, Section 508, etc. explained when used)
      - CTAs use action-oriented, benefit-driven language
    </content_quality>
  </success_criteria>
</project_specification>
